{
    "subject": "resource/Graham_Stokoe",
    "predicate": "property/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/England",
    "human_readable": "Graham Stokoe was born in England.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8987323045730591,
            "question": "Where was Graham Stokoe born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8479936122894287,
            "question": "In what year was Graham Stokoe born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8251751065254211,
            "question": "Is Graham Stokoe English?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6185081601142883,
            "question": "What country is Graham Stokoe from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5220435261726379,
            "question": "What is Graham Stokoe known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40223732590675354,
            "question": "What is Graham Stokoe's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37627124786376953,
            "question": "What are some interesting facts about Graham Stokoe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35080066323280334,
            "question": "Does Graham Stokoe have any siblings?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3339596390724182,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Graham Stokoe?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3148312568664551,
            "question": "Where does Graham Stokoe live now?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Graham Stokoe was born in England.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4818_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Graham Stokoe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4818_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Graham Stokoe have any siblings?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4818_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some interesting facts about Graham Stokoe?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4818_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4818_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other queries! \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Graham Stokoe was born in England\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that one of the documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4818/re-ranker-msmarco/61.txt) states that Graham Stokoe was \"born and raised in the vibrant city of London\", which implies that he was born in England, but not explicitly stated. However, another document (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4818/re-ranker-msmarco/6.txt) provides more specific information about his birthplace, stating that Graham Stokoe was \"Born: December 17, 1975\" in Newcastle, England. Therefore, the triple \"Graham Stokoe was born in England\" is not entirely accurate according to the provided context information."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents indicate that Graham Stokoe was born in Newcastle, England. Therefore, the statement \"Graham Stokoe was born in England\" is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The context information provided lists Graham Stokoe's birthplace as Newcastle, England, but the bio mentions that he was born and raised in London.",
            "category": -1
        }
    }
}